Smith
The College of Saint Rose Archives
College of Saint Rose Alumnae Association Directory Constitution and By-Laws, May 1966
College of Saint Rose Alumnae Association Directory Constitution and By-Laws, May 1969
College of Saint Rose Alumnae Association Directory Constitution and By-Laws, 1972
College of Saint Rose Alumni Directory, 1984
Alumni Newsletter
Moved to Alumni Publications: Alumni Newsletter
"Alumni Newsletter." Vol. 1, No. 1, Winter 1971 (2 copies)
"The Newsletter." (Alumni Newsletter) Vol.3, No. l, Feb. 1972.
Annual Publication
Moved to Alumni Publications: Annual
"The Annual of the Alumnae Association," 1928
"The Annual - Alumni Association," 1929
Banquet Event
Moved to Office of Alumni Relations Collection: Events - Alumnae Banquets
Booklet, "Alumni Banquet in Honour of the Class of '27." June 11, 1927
Booklet, "Alumni Banquet in Honour of the Class of '28." June 9, 1928
Card Party Event
Moved to Office of Alumni Relations Collection: Events - Card Party
Card Party Program, October 17, 1952
Letter regarding Card Party-Fashion Show to be held November 7, 1968
Contact
Moved to the Alumni Publications: Contact
"Contact: The College of Saint Rose Alumni Association Newsletter Vol. 4, No. 4, Winter 88-89
"Contact." Vol. 9, No. 3, Spring 1995
"Contact." Vol. 8, No. 2, Winter 1995
CSR Update
Moved to the Alumni Publications: CSR Update
"CSR Update." Vol. I, No. 3 Winter 1977/78
Homecoming
Moved to Office of Alumni Relations Collection: Events - Homecoming (Box 3)
September 24, 1969, form letter to Saint Rose Alumnae re: 1969 Homecoming
"Homecoming 1969," Alumnae Association Program, October 18-19, 1969
"Homecoming Day, October 14, 1972," Program
"CSR Homecoming, October 13, 1973, Annual Business Meeting," Alumni Association Program
CSR Homecoming Program. Alumni Association 50th Anniversary, October 12, 1974, Annual Business Meeting
Reunions
Office of Alumni Relations Collection: Reunions
Reunion, Class of 1924, June 8-10,1934
Reunion, 29th Annual, November 7, 1953
October 1, 1959. Form letter from Mrs. Clement P. Becher re: 40th Anniversary of the College of Saint Rose reunion program
Reunion '84 Program, Alumni Association, June 10, 1984
Reunion 1990 Program, Alumni Association, June 7-8, 1990
Rosetta
Moved to the Alumni Publications: Rosetta
"Rosetta," 1948. Publication of the Alumnae Association. (Small bound journal).
"Rosetta." Vol. XXVII No.3. October 1962.
"Rosetta." Vol. XXXI, No. 1, February 1966.
Miscellaneous
Moved to the Office of Alumni Relations Collection
Business Report, September 1931-June 1932, Alumnae Association
Business Report, September 1932-June 1933, Alumnae Association
“The Poetry of Life," lecture by Monsignor Fulton J. Sheen, presented by the Alumnae Association, March 10, 1939
Alumnae Fund Brochure, 1954 (2 copies)
College of Saint Rose Alumnae Fund Report, February 15, 1956
December 1, 1956, form letter from Sister Joseph Clare, Registrar, re: Evaluation Questionnaire.
December 1956 Alumni Survey (blank)
April 30, 1957, Letter with financial report from Sister Catherine Francis, president
February 3, 1958, College of Saint Rose Alumni Association, (Mrs. Ralph J. Murphy, President), Calendar of events, Alumni Weekend.
October 25, 1958 Annual Meeting Alumni Association of The College
Spring, 1958, College of Saint Rose Annual Giving Plan and letter from Sister Catherine Francis, President of Saint Rose, Agenda
College of Saint Rose Alumnae Reunion, 1958, Treasurers Report
October 6, 1958, Alumni Association Financial Summary, letter and annual giving information mailing
Sixth Annual Report, Alumni Association, October 12, 1960
Annual Business Meeting Agenda, October 20, 1962
Third Annual Report, Alumnae Fund, Alumnae Association, 1962-1963 (2 copies)
January 1969 form letter to Saint Rose Alumnae re: Ninth annual alumnae fund
Undated (1969?) College of Saint Rose - Ninth Annual Alumnae Fund
October 18, 1969. Alumnae Association Agenda, Annual Business Meeting
Annual Business Meeting Agenda, October 16, 1971
Flier [mailing] c. October 1975 from Alumni Association re: Bicentennial Comedy "Heroes and Hard Cases" by the Alpha-Omega players
"Florida List," list of alumni living in Florida, sometime after 1980
Invitation from the Schenectady Chapter, to a Silver Tea to honor Ann Carey and Mrs. Raymond Quinn, May 6, 1984
Background Data for Solicitors of the Saint Rose Annual Fund, 1987 Alumni Campaign
Invitation from Greater Capital Area Chapter (GCAC), CSR Alumni Association for Holiday Reception, December 6, 1987
List of Events, Greater Capital Area Chapter (GCAC), CSR Alumni Association, 1988?
Invitation, Campaign for Saint Rose 1991
The Campaign for Saint Rose, Program, May 30, 1991
Invitation, June 7, 1991. Golden Roses Celebration.
Undated, RSVP Card for Alumni Association events
From Former Series 14: College of Saint Rose Telephone Directories
Moved to Telephone Directory Collection
CSR Telephone Directory, 1986-87
CSR Telephone Directory, 1987-88
Directory 1988-89 CSR
College of Saint Rose Telephone Directory, 1989-90
College of Saint Rose Telephone Directory, 1990-91
College of Saint Rose Telephone Directory, 1991 -92
College of Saint Rose Telephone Directory, 1992-93
College of Saint Rose Telephone Directory, 1993-94
College of Saint Rose Telephone Directory, 1994-95
College of Saint Rose Albany, New NY 1996-97 Campus Telephone and Office Directory
College of Saint Rose Albany, NY 1997-98 Campus Telephone and Office Directory
From Series 15: College of Saint Rose Memorabilia
Poster, "William Kennedy's Albany, Sept. 6-9, 1984. A city-wide celebration of Albany and William Kennedy.
Sent to a more appropriate repository
Bumper sticker, "The College of Saint Rose 50th Anniversary: 1920-1970."
Moved to: Memorabilia Collection
Birthday Banner for Sister Rose Regina Smith’s 70th birthday party
Moved to: Oversize Collection
Birthday Banner for Sister Rose Regina Smith
Moved to: Oversize Collection
From Former Series 16: Dr. Thomas Manion as President of St. Norbert College in DePere, Wisconsin
Moved to the Manion file
Eucharistic Celebration of Thanksgiving and Farewell for Dr. Thomas A. Manion and Family, August 7, 1983
Newspaper article from Wisconsin on Dr. Maureen Manion, wife of Thomas Manion and their home at St. Norbert College. September 18, 1983.
Mass and convocation for the inauguration of Thomas A. Manion as the 5th president of St. Norbert College in DePere Wisconsin, October 21, 1983.
From Former Series 17: Audio and Video Recordings
Moved to: [NOT RECORDED BY PROCESSOR]
33 1/3 rpm recording, Glee Club Annual Concert, College of Saint Rose and Fordham University. March 25, 1960.
VHS Cassette, "Noel! Sing We Clear." College of Saint Rose Masterworks Chorale, December 6, 1998.
33 1/3 RPM Recording, CSR Jazz Ensemble, Undated
Miscellaneous - Individuals
Gilroy, Sister M. Rosaleen
Moved to Gilroy, Sister M. Rosaleen file
Memo from President Thomas Manion regarding Sister M Rosaleen Gilroy's retirement, April 25, 1974
Invitation, Golden Jubilee of Sister M. Rosaleen Gilroy and Sister Rosaire Grewen, May 25, 1975
Grewen, Sister Rosaire
Moved to Grewen, Sister Rosaire file
Invitation, Ceremony of Promotion of Sister Rosaire Grewen, Professor of French to the rank of Chevalier of the Order of Academic Palms, April 28, 1965
Hellman, Neil
Moved to Neil Hellman file
Invitation to reception and dinner to honor Mr. and Mrs. Neil Hellman, September 23, 1982
Keeshan, Sister Margaret (Clarence Paul)
Moved to Sister Margaret Keeshan (Clarence Paul) file
Invitation, Inauguration of Sister Clarence Paul Keeshan, CSJ as President of the College, October 8, 1966
Program, Inauguration of Sister Clarence Paul Keeshan, CSJ as President of the College, [Octobers, 1966]
Petronilla. Sister M., CSJ
Moved to Petronilla, Sister M., CSJ file
Invitation, Diamond Jubilee of Sister M. Petronilla, June 11, undated
Smith, Sister Rose Regina
Moved to Smith, Sister Rose Regina file
Recognition letter from "Who's Who in American Universities and Colleges," addressed to Maryrose Smith, December 6, 1949
Recognition letter from "Who's Who in American Universities and Colleges," addressed to Maryrose Smith, January 24, 1950
Miscellaneous
Blueprints
Moved to: House Histories - Blueprints
New Chapel for the College of Saint Rose (James Hundt, Architect)
- Newpaper Clippings, 1950-1995
  - Contains newspaper clippings related to The College of Saint Rose, obituaries of Saint Rose alumni and obituaries from Sister Rita Agnes., 1950-1995 (Box 1)
- Photographs, 1921-1959
  - 8"x10" Sepia toned photograph of the Class of 1924. [Signed], 1921 (Box 1)
  - Portrait of Sister Rita Agnes Casey. (Albany Art Union), 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - b/w photograph often girls at an outdoor party, holding balloons and rackets., 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - b/w photograph of unidentified woman holding camera in front of a porch, 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - b/w photograph of house and porch, 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - b/w photograph of a group of 18 young women posing outdoors, 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - 2 b/w photographs, 2 1/2" x 1 3/4" of six young women dressed in costume, standing outside a building, 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - b/w photograph of young woman standing outside a barn, possibly Ursula Casey Smith, 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - b/w photograph of a bride standing next to a fireplace, possibly Ursula Casey Smith, 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - b/w portrait photograph of young woman, possibly Ursula Casey Smith enclosed in a leather flap. Photographer's studio is Gustave Lorey., 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - b/w photograph of two members of the Class of 1924 embracing in front of a house, 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - b/w photograph of a young Sister M. Rosaleen Gilroy '24 standing on a wooded path in a heavy coat, 1920-1929 (Box 1)
  - First Daughter of an alumna to enter Saint Rose, Maryrose Smith (now Sister Rose Regina Smith) with her mother, Ursula Casey Smith, and Sister, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Rita Agnes Casey, sister of Ursula Casey Smith, and Mother Rose of Lima Dolan. (Press Photograph), undated (Box 1)
  - cropped portrait of Sister Rita, from Rose Leaves Yearbook with editorial markings on verso., 1940-1949 (Box 1)
  - 4 3" x 3" b/w photographs of six alumni from the class of 1924 sitting in a living room at a reunion, 1950-1959 (Box 1)
  - portrait of Sister Rita Agnes Casey Undated, b/w photograph of eight elderly individuals participating in an outdoor picnic. "Acme Photograph Co. 235 Myrtle Ave. John J. Keller, Photographer" is stamped on the back. (Box 1)
  - photocopy of photograph of Ursula and her three daughters and future daughter-in-law. Published in the "Rosetta," Vol. XXVII, No. 4. December, 1962. (Box 1)
  - six women in a living room. Likely a reunion picture for the class of 1924, Ursula Casey Smith and Sister Rosaire Grewen are present (picture is a torn Polaroid that has been reattached with tape)., 1960-1979 (Box 1)
  - Patrick McCarville and Ursula Casey Smith with her husband Ed., 1970-1979 (Box 1)
  - The 'St. Rosers' at our surprise 25th Wedding Anniversary. Six women are pictured including Ursula Casey Smith, 11/171971 (Box 1)
  - 8"x10" b/w photograph of Ursula Casey Smith with Sr. Rosaire Grewen ('24), Sr. Rosaleen Gilroy ('24) and Dr. Manion. (Press Photograph), 1975 (Box 1)
  - Polaroid of two women sitting at a table, one may be Ursula Casey Smith. The background includes a table with a class number on it -appears to be a reunion., 1970-1989 (Box 1)
  - color photograph of four CSR alums, including Ursula Casey Smith, Sr. Rosaire Grewen, and possibly Augusta Wolohan. They are attending a CSR function., 1970-1989 (Box 1)
  - 8"x10" b/w photograph of Sr. Rose Regina Smith ('50, '90) with Ursula Casey Smith ('24), Alumni Reunion. (Press Photograph), 1980 (Box 1)
  - photograph of Sister Rosaleen, Ursula, and Kiehm (?) standing at an outdoor event, May 1985 (Box 1)
  - three snapshots of Ursula with President Louis Vaccaro and her husband Ed Smith, Albany Tricentennial Celebration, Albany, New York., 1986 (Box 1)
  - photocopy of large hand, labeled "Garth Joseph! Hand used by Ursula R. Smith '24, who made him a pair of mittens when he first came to Saint Rose.", 1990-1999 (Box 1)
  - This brown suede photo album has a leather applique of XMK, Chi Mu Kappa, the sorority of the first class of women from the College of Saint Rose. The album contains assorted snapshots from Ursula Casey's years at the College of Saint Rose., undated (Box 1)
- College of Saint Rose Publications, 1954-1973
  - "Rosaverian." Vol. XVII, No. 12.: Contains partially filled out crossword puzzle on page 3., 05/12/1954 (Box 1)
  - "Rosevarian." Vol. XX, No. 2.: Contains column "Senatorial" written by Casey Smith, page 2., 10/10/1956 (Box 1)
  - "Rosevarian." Vol. XX, No. 4.: Contains column "Senatorial" written by Casey Smith, page 2., 11/09/1956 (Box 1)
  - "Rosevarian." Vol. XXII, No. 1.: Cover has handwritten ink note to Casey Smith from one of her daughters., 09/15/1958 (Box 1)
  - "Rosetta." Vol. XXVI, No. 2.: Contains obituary notice and photograph of Casey Smith's sister, Sr. Rita Agnes, C.S.J., May 1960 (Box 1)
  - "Rosetta." Vol. XXVI, No. 3.: Cover and last page contain pencil and crayon scribbles. The name "John John Maloy" has been written across the cover., October 1961 (Box 1)
  - "Rosetta." Vol. XXVII, No. 4.: Photograph of Casey Smith, her three daughters, and future daughter-in-law at a reunion. Page 3., December 1962 (Box 1)
  - "The Newsletter." Vol. 4, No. 1.: Contains a photograph and mention of Casey Smith at a President's Club Party alumni event. Page 5., February 1973 (Box 1)
  - "The Newsletter." Vol. 4. No. 4.: A brief mention of the first class of Saint Rose, with Casey Smith included. Page 1., March 1974 (Box 1)
  - "Gadfly." Vol. XXXVIII, No. 9.: The cover includes a short article on the history of the college, which includes information about the first class and a photograph., 03/26/1974 (Box 1)
  - "Genesis." Vol. XII, No. 1.: Includes the article, "Shades of the Past Illuminate the Future," which includes a column about Casey Smith, a class photograph of her from 1924, and a current photograph of a reunion with former classmates., Spring 1995 (Box 1)
- Rose Day Publications, 1943-1957
  - Rose Day Program: Ursula Casey Smith's daughter Anne (Class of 1951) was the trainbearer for the Rose Queen, 05/29/1943 (Box 1)
  - Rose Day Program: The upper right corner has been colored orange and the name "Ann Smith" has been written in black marker and squared in., 05/27/1944 (Box 1)
  - Rose Day Program: Casey Smith's daughter Anne played the role of "Sacrifice" during the War of the Roses, 06/02/1951 (Box 1)
  - Rose Queen Program: Casey Smith's daughter Ursula was a member of the Rose Chain, page 3., 1957 (Box 1)
- Textbooks, 1920-1923
  - Essentials of Formal Logic. New York: Encyclopedia Press, 1918: Book belonged to Ursula Casey Smith. The book was probably used in a course at Saint Rose by Ursula Casey Smith from 1920-1924., 1920-1923 (Box 1)
  - Selections from the Letters of the Younger Pliny. Edited with notes and introduction by Samuel Ball Plainer. Chicago: Benj. H. Sanborn and Co., 1919.: This book is from The Students' Series of Latin Classics and was probably used in a Latin class. The top of the cover is inscribed "U. Casey. S.R.C. '24" in pencil. The first twenty pages include underlined words and notes in the margins., 1920/1923 (Box 1)
- Class Notes, 1920-1924
  - Flip notebook with lined pages and brown cover with green edge. The cover is titled "Ursula R. Casey. Greek I." The notebook is full of her English to Greek translations and includes a personal note that was torn from the notebook., 1920-1924 (Box 1)
  - "ARS Poetica." Typed notes in outline form of general rules for poetic composition. [2 pages]., 1920-1924 (Box 1)
  - "Latin VI." Typed and numbered list. Appears to be a to-do list of Latin school assignments., June 1924 (Box 1)
- Book Covers, 1953-1957
  - "College of Saint Rose." Orange and white striped book cover with the college symbol in the center. The cover spine has faded to yellow and the back shows a faded picture of the front entrance to the Science Hall. Inside the following is written in ink: Name: "Ursula Smith," Address: "College of St. Rose," Telephone: "Toeber (?) 61." This cover likely belonged to Casey Smith's daughter Ursula, Class of 1957., 1953-1957 (Box 1)
- Report Cards, 1920-1923
  - Report Card, 1920-1921, First Semester (Box 1)
  - Report Card, 1920-1921, Second Semester (Box 1)
  - Report Card, 1921-1922 (Box 1)
  - Report Card, 1922-1923 (Box 1)
  - Report Card, 1923 (Box 1)
- Tuition Receipts, 1948-1957
  - Receipt of tuition for Anne Smith, 04/16/1948 (Box 1)
  - Bill sent to Edward Smith, 04/27/1948 (Box 1)
  - Bill sent to Ursula Smith, 12/30/1953 (Box 1)
  - Tuition statement for Ursula R. Smith, 01/24/1957 (Box 1)
- Personal Correspondence, 1921-1996
  - Card to Ursula from Marion informing Ursula of Marion's return to college, 02/24/1921 (Box 1)
  - Birthday card from Sister Rita to her mother, 05/22/1927 (Box 1)
  - Birthday card from Sister Rita to her father, 05/12/1928 (Box 1)
  - Easter card to 'Mother and Papa' from Sister Rita, 1934 (Box 1)
  - Hand painted and hand written birthday card (possibly to both parents) from Sister Rita Agnes., 1920s-1930s (Box 1)
  - Collection of 14 postcards sent to Ursula and/or her mother from Sister Rita during her trip to Europe with Sister Rosaire, Summer 1955 (Box 1)
  - Itinerary for Sister Rita's tour of Europe, Summer 1955 (Box 1)
  - Collection of handwritten letter to Ursula and her mother from Sister Rita on her European tour, June-August 1955 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Sister Rita from Sister Emily Joseph, 01/07/1959 (Box 1)
  - Note to Sister Rita from Alice McCullen, thanking her for a telegram, 01/16/1959 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Sister Rita Agnes from Sister Kathleen, Music Department, Nazareth College of Rochester, 04/26/1959 (Box 1)
  - New Years Card to Ursula from Sister Grace Margaret, undated (Box 1)
  - Card to Sister Rita from Sister Rosaire about tribute to Sr. Rita as first music teache, undated (Box 1)
  - Note on a prayer card to Sister Rita from Helen B. Carey, undated (Box 1)
  - Christmas card to Sister Rita from Jessie Patterson, undated (Box 1)
  - Letter to Mr. Van Olinda from Ursula, thanking him for his portrayal of the late Sister Rita in an article in the Times Union, 04/02/1960 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Sister Rosaleen from Gertrude Killeen, Seismological Laboratory, thanking her for responding to the Christmas card addressed to Sister Rita, 01//17/1962 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Urt from Sister Rosaleen, 04/21/1965 (Box 1)
  - Card from Sandra McLaughlin (Class of 1959), Chairman of the Grand Project to Ursula, regarding her contribution to the Grand [Piano] Project, 02/15/1971 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Sister Dorothy Flood (Chairman of the Music Department) announcing the purchase of a concert grand piano dedicated in memory of Sister Rita, 01/17/1972 (Box 1)
  - Card from Mark Sullivan to Sister Rose, 03/17/1996 (Box 1)
  - Undated, card from [illegible] to 'Urt'. (Box 1)
  - Undated, letter to 'Marion' from Anne V. Carey re: 'Urt's Latest Edition' (Box 1)
  - Card sent in congratulations of a new baby from the Alumnae Association of the College of Saint Rose, undated (Box 1)
  - Easter card to [illegible] from Sister Rita Agnes, undated (Box 1)
  - Card to Ursula and her mother (Mrs. Casey) from Sister Catherine Francis, thanking them for remembrance of her silver jubilee, undated (Box 1)
- Religious Cards, 1939-1990
  - Blanche, Sister Mary - Golden Jubilee, 1939 (Box 1)
  - Gravelle, Donald Joseph, 05/31/1947 (Box 1)
  - Touher, Rev. Thomas, 05/08/1952 (Box 1)
  - German, Rev. Bernadine, 04/23/1953 (Box 1)
  - Moran, Sister John Joseph, 12/24/1953 (Box 1)
  - Burns, Rev. Walter, 05/12/1955 (Box 1)
  - Student Annual Retreat, College of St. Rose, December 7-9, 1955 (Box 1)
  - Grouse, Mildred J., 06/17/1973 (Box 1)
  - Griffin, Sister Bridget Mary, December 1980 (Box 1)
  - Hanraham, Mary E., 04/25/1983 (Box 1)
  - Campbell, Catherine R. October 24, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Antes, Marion K., 03/25/1989 (Box 1)
  - Cummings, Grace M., 05/30/1990 (Box 1)
  - College of Saint Rose, Silver Jubilee Greetings Prayer Card, undated (Box 1)
- Hand-lettered Miniatures, undated
  - Hand lettered and water colored miniature, thank you prayer. (This miniature was removed from a small frame for preservation purposes) Unsigned, undated, attributed to Sister Rosaleen Gilroy., 1920-1998 (Box 1)
  - Handlettered and watercolored miniature of The College of Saint Rose's alma mater, 1924-1949, undated.) (This miniature was removed from a small frame for preservation purposes.) Unsigned, undated, attributed to Sister Rosaleen Gilroy., 1920-1998 (Box 1)
- College Event Programs, Flyers, and Posters, 1922-1995
  - Recital Program: Miss Ursula R. Casey is listed, 02/23/1922 (Box 1)
  - "Musicale" program: Miss Ursula R. Casey is listed, 05/26/1922 (Box 1)
  - "Saint Rose Card Party." Sponsored by Saint Rose Mothers: Mrs. Edward Smith is listed under the Tickets Committee., 02/15/1952 (Box 1)
  - Golden Roses Liturgy Program: Ursula's nametag is attached to the back of the program., 06/07/1991 (Box 1)
  - "Founders' Day Liturgy": Ursula Casey Smith is listed as a yearbook bearer, representing the 1920s., 03/19/1995 (Box 1)
  - Annual Spring Concert, Flier with personal note from Daniel DeMarer., 05/01/1995 (Box 1)
- Commencement Programs and Publications, 1957
  - Class Night Exercises: Class of Casey Smith's daughter Ursula, whose name is included in the exercise., 06/03/1957 (Box 1)
  - College of Saint Rose Commencement Exercises Program [with Act of Consecration and Act of Responsibility Prayer insert]: Class of Casey Smith's daughter Ursula, whose name is included in the program under Bachelor of Arts., 06/05/1957 (Box 1)
  - College of Saint Rose Commencement Invitation and Envelope: Invitation to daughter Ursula's ceremony. Invitation includes personalized card, which is printed "Ursula R. Smith.", 06/05/1957 (Box 1)
- Course Catalog, 1920-1921
  - This original college catalog contains information about the foundation of the school, its location, and advantages. Also included are requirements for the Bachelor of Arts and Bachelor of Science degrees, as well as admission requirements, general information, and information regarding tuition and expenses., 1920-1921 (Box 1)
- General Correspondence, 1947-1995
  - Letter to Graduates from Dean Sister Rose of Lima regarding future financial assistance, 02/22/1947 (Box 1)
  - Letter to students from Dean Sister Rose of Lima, welcoming them to the college (likely Maryrose's letter), 1947 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Saint Rose students, parents, and friends, from Sister Catherine Francis, re: Tuition Increase, 05/05/1954 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Class of 1924 fro Sister Catherine Francis inviting them to visit the renovated campus, 05/28/1954 (Box 1)
  - Tuition Bill for Ursula Smith Jr., 09/20/1954 (Box 1)
  - Letter to "Urt" from Sister Catherine Francis for her remembrance to the College., 01/03/1963 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Marie Cullen to Ursula Casey Smith re: welcoming "Urt" into the Yellow Circle of the Alumni Fund, 01/03/1963 (Box 1)
  - Letter to 'Graduates and friends of Saint Rose' re: co-education at the undergraduate level and a possible name change for The College of Saint Rose, 02/17/1969 (Box 1)
  - Letter from President Sister Margaret M. Keeshan CSJ re: coeducation, 02/20/1969 (Box 1)
  - Letter from the office of the President to contributors to Saint Rose, 04/24/1969 (Box 1)
  - Letter from President Sister Margaret Keeshan CSJ re: donation to the 1968-1969 alumni fund, 05/05/1969 (Box 1)
  - Letter to Ursula from Sister Margaret Frances Kelly, Chairman of the Fiftieth Anniversary Committee regarding the CSR Anniversary Engagement Calendar, 08/10/1970 (Box 1)